<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>飞出国加拿大签证大全</title>
    <link>http://us.cgvisa.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 飞出国加拿大签证大全</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-CN</language>
    <atom:link href="http://us.cgvisa.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>加拿大商务访问签证</title>
      <link>http://us.cgvisa.com/2742/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://us.cgvisa.com/2742/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;加拿大商务访问签证&#34;&gt;加拿大商务访问签证&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大商务访问签证申请条件-飞出国&#34;&gt;加拿大商务访问签证申请条件 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;商务访问人员指的是打算临时访问加拿大来从事以下3方面业务的人员：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;寻求新的方式来拓展您的业务，&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;投资；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;推动业务关系。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;加拿大商务访问人员要求 business visitor - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt; ：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;访问时间不超过6个月；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;不会涉足加拿大劳动力市场；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;你的主要业务，收入来源和利润，均不在加拿大境内；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;有申请要求的材料；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;满足加拿大基本入境要求（飞出国）：

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;有效的旅行文件，如护照；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;足够的资金支持你在加拿大的花销以及返程机票；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;按时离境；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;不会给加拿大人带来犯罪、安全和健康风险；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;跨境业务可以包括 Cross-border business - 飞出国：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;为外国企业或政府购买加拿大商品或服务，&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;订购商品或服务，&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;参加会议或交易会；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;提供售后服务（管理，不会亲自劳动）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;参加加拿大总公司的培训，然后去加拿大以外的国家工作；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;为国外公司在加拿大分公司的雇员提供培训；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;参加加拿大出售给你设备或服务的公司的培训。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大访问签证境内延期政策-飞出国&#34;&gt;加拿大访问签证境内延期政策 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;如果临时签证到期后还想继续留在加拿大一段时间的话，需要申请签证延期。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;签证延期要在签证到期日前30天申请。到期日可以在学习许可或工作许可上查到，护照上也会有邮戳，如果护照上没有邮戳日期，到期日是从你入境那天开始，往后推迟6个月。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;加拿大访问签证境内延期申请流程 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;可以在线申请也可以纸质申请，以下介绍纸质申请。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. 准备所有需要的表格材料（飞出国）；&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;详见材料清单。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. 支付申请费（飞出国）；&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;费用：&lt;/strong&gt;100加币。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;支付方式：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;用信用卡在线支付（推荐使用）；&lt;br /&gt;
或者：&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; For option 2:&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; We will need to mail you an original receipt. It may take two to three weeks to arrive.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; Bring this receipt to pay your fees at the bank or wire service. They will keep one section and give the rest back to you.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; Send one section with your application and keep the other for your records.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. 递交申请（飞出国）。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;将所有材料邮寄到 Case Processing Centre in Vegreville, Alberta，地址：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CPC Vegreville&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;strong&gt;Visitor and Temporary Resident Permit&lt;/strong&gt;
&amp;gt; 6212-55th Avenue – Unit 303&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; Vegreville, AB&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; T9C 1W1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;加拿大访问签证境内延期材料清单 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;所有申请人都需要提供的材料：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IMM5708] 访问签证延期申请表；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IMM5558] 清单表；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IMM5401] 收据；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IMM5476] 代理表（如适用）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IMM5409] 同居伴侣法定声明（如有）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;结婚证书复印件（如有）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;护照首页和加拿大签证页的复印件；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;当前移民文件复印件（如有）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proof of means of support；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;返程机票复印件（如有）。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;商务访问材料清单-针对个人-飞出国&#34;&gt;商务访问材料清单（针对个人） - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Checklist for Personal or Professional Affairs (Attending an Academic Conference, Exploratory Visits, Legal Matters) Temporary Resident Visa Application&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;个人或专业事宜   (参加学术会议、考察访问，法律事宜)临时居留签证申请审核表&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Completed  “Application  for  a  Temporary  Resident  Visa” (IMM  5257).  An  Application   form  is  required  for  each applicant, including each accompanying child. 填写完整的“临时居民访问签证申请表 (IMM5257）”。每 位申请人及每名随行子女均需一份单独的申请表格。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Completed  “Family  Information”  form (IMM  5645)  for  you and each accompanying family member aged 18 years old and  above, completed in English or French AND Chinese.
申请人及每位年满 18 周岁及以上的随行家庭成员完整填写“家庭信息表”（IMM5645），请使用中英文或中法文填写。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Completed  “Education  and  Employment”  form  for  you  and each  accompanying  family  member  aged  18  years  old  and above, completed in English or French AND Chinese. 申请人及每位年满 18 周岁及以上的随行家庭成员完整填写 “教育和就业细节表”，请使用中英文或中法文填写。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two (2) identical   photos  of  the applicant   and each accompanying family member, colour or black and white taken    against a plain white or light coloured background within the   last 6 months. The frame size is 35mm X 45mm. On the back of one photo in each set, write the name in pinyin and date of birth (day/month/year) of the person appearing in the photo.&lt;br /&gt;
申请人及每位随行的家庭成员每人需递交两张相同的在最近六个月内拍摄的彩色或黑白照片，背景为纯白色或浅色。相片外框大小为 35 毫米 X 45 毫米。每张照片后以拼音注明此人的姓名及出生日期（日/月/年）。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A  valid  passport  for  the  applicant  and  each  accompanying family  member.  There  must  be  one  completely  blank  page other than the last page, available in each passport and each passport must be valid for at least six (6) months prior to travel&lt;br /&gt;
申请人及每位随行的家庭成员的有效护照。每本护照须包含除最后一页外的至少一整页空白页、且护照必须在行程前至少六个月有效。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Copy of your national identity document (two sides)
申请人本人中国身份证复印件(正反面)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two  (2)  self-addressed  adhesive  labels  with  the  applicant’s current address in Chinese characters (no envelope). 两份用中文写有申请人现住址的粘性贴纸 (无需信封)。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The correct application processing fee paid in cash. Fee is non- refundable. 以现金支付正确的申请受理费。受理费不予退还。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Use of a Representative” form (IMM5476E) if someone has assisted you in making this application. 如有第三方人士帮助你准备此次申请，请填写代理人信息表
（IMM5476E）。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;For children less than 18 years old, Parental Letter of Consent from your non-accompanying parent(s) authorizing  your travel. This letter should contain the dates of travel and your parent(s)’s contact information.
18 岁以下的申请人需有其未随行父/母出具的同意其旅行的 父母同意函，此函应包含申请人旅行日期及其父母联系方式
等信息。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If applicant is employed, a signed original letter on company letterhead from the employer granting leave of absence and including the following information:
name, position, current salary and date of hire; and
employer’s name and address in Chinese characters as well as email, website address, telephone and fax number; 如果在职，使用印有公司抬头信笺、由雇主签字的准假信原 件，并包含以下信息： 申请人的姓名、职位、目前收入及起聘日期；以及 用中文注明的雇主全称和地址，以及电子邮件、网址、电话 和传真号码；&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If applicant or applicant’s company intends to invest in Canada applicant must provide evidence of sufficient assets to make the proposed investment (e.g. business registration, articles of association,  company  tax  receipts,  sales  contracts,  balance sheets, company brochures, etc.) 如果计划在加拿大投资，必须提供其具备充足资产以进行预 期投资的证据 ( 如公司注册证明、公司章程、公司缴税凭 据、销售合同、资产负债表、公司手册，等)。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Original bank documents showing financial  history  over several months (e.g. Certificates of Deposits, bank books, etc.) 显示过去若干月中财政历史的银行文件原件(如存款证明、 存折等)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evidence of assets in China (e.g. original property certificate, vehicle registration, etc.).
在中国的资产证明 (如房产证原件、车辆登记证明原件等)。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;An  invitation  letter  or  conference  registration  stating  the purpose and duration of the visit. 说明访问目的及访问期限的邀请函或会议注册函&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大商务访问材料清单-针对公司-飞出国&#34;&gt;加拿大商务访问材料清单（针对公司） - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Checklist for Business (Company to Company International Business Activities, or Trade Shows) Temporary Resident Visa Application&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;商务访问 (公司间的国际商务活动、或贸易会展) 临时居留签证申请审核表&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Completed “Application for a Temporary Resident Visa” (IMM 5257). An Application form is required for each applicant, including each accompanying child.
填写完整的“临时居民访问签证申请表 (IMM5257）”。每位申请人及每名随行子女均需一份单独的申请表格。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Completed “Family Information” form (IMM 5645)  for  you and each accompanying family member aged 18 years old and above, completed in English or French AND Chinese.
申请人及每位年满 18 周岁及以上的随行家庭成员完整填写“家庭信息表”（IMM5645），请使用中英文或中法文填写。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two (2) identical   photos  of  the applicant   and each accompanying family member, colour or black and white taken against a plain white or light coloured background within the  last 6 months. The frame size is 35mm X 45mm. On the back of one photo in each set, write the name in pinyin and date of    birth (day/month/year) of the person appearing in the photo.
申请人及每位随行的家庭成员每人需递交两张相同的在最近六个月内拍摄的彩色或黑白照片，背景为纯白色或浅色。相片外框大小为 35 毫米 X 45 毫米。每张照片后以拼音注明此人的姓名及出生日期（日/月/年）。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A  valid  passport  for  the  applicant  and  each  accompanying family  member.  There  must  be  one  completely  blank  page other than the last page, available in each passport and each passport must be valid for at least six (6) months prior to travel
申请人及每位随行的家庭成员的有效护照。每本护照须包含除最后一页外的至少一整页空白页、且护照必须在行程前至少六个月有效。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two  (2)  self-addressed  adhesive  labels  with  the  applicant’s current address in Chinese characters (no envelope). 两份用中文写有申请人现住址的粘性贴纸 (无需信封)。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The correct application processing fee paid in cash. Fee is non- refundable. 以现金支付正确的申请受理费。受理费不予退还。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Use of a Representative” form (IMM5476E) if someone has assisted you in making this application.
如有第三方人士帮助你准备此次申请，请填写代理人信息表（IMM5476E）。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;For children less than 18 years old, Parental Letter of Consent from your non-accompanying parent(s) authorizing  your travel. This letter should contain the dates of travel and your parent(s)’s contact information.
18 岁以下的申请人需有其未随行父/母出具的同意其旅行的父母同意函，此函应包含申请人旅行日期及其父母联系方式 等信息。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are engaging in Company to Company business activities: A letter of invitation from the party in Canada. The invitation letter must come from the party with whom you will conduct direct business. This excludes third parties who are only arranging or facilitating the business meetings. The letter must include all of the following information:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;inviter’s  full  name  and  title,  business  address,  email, website address, telephone and fax numbers;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;names and titles of all members of the delegation, as well as the name(s) of their employer(s);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a brief summary of the reason for the invitation including details of the business or trade to be undertaken;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the  intended  duration  of  the  visit  as  well  as  a  detailed itinerary;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a  statement  specifying  who  will  be  responsible  for  all expenses related to the trip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;若你从事公司间的商务活动：来自于加方的邀请信。邀请信必须由与申请人进行直接业务往来的一方出具，而非来 自于只协助安排商务会议的第三方。该信必须包含所有以 下信息：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;邀请人的全称及职务、公司地址、电话和传真号码；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;团组所有成员的姓名及分别的职务、以及其分别雇主的 全称；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;邀请缘由的简述、其中包含将要进行的商务或贸易详 情；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;预期的访问期限及详细行程安排；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;说明此次旅行所有相关费用支付责任的声明，以及&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10.If you are attending a trade show or other business conference: A letter from the conference organizer confirming your registration.
若你参加贸易会展或其他商务会议：来自于会议组织方的确认你已注册的信函&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;11.A signed original letter on company letterhead from the Chinese employer indicating that the  proposed  travel  to Canada has been approved. This letter must include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the purpose of travel;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the employer’s name and address in Chinese characters as well as telephone and fax number;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;applicant’s position, salary and date of hire; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a  statement  specifying  who  will  be  responsible  for  all expenses related to the trip.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;一份使用印有公司抬头信笺由中方雇主签发的准假信原件，此信必须包含：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;旅行目的；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;用中文注明的雇主全称和地址、以及电话和传真号码；&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;申请人的职务、收入和起聘日期；以及&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;说明此次旅行所有相关费用支付责任的声明。&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;以上内容由飞出国论坛（&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com&#34;&gt;FCGvisa.com&lt;/a&gt;）独家整理完成，请尊重知识产权，转载请保留并注明出处。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>加拿大学习许可</title>
      <link>http://us.cgvisa.com/2876/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://us.cgvisa.com/2876/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;加拿大学习许可:a274789a363a6b1dac89da47ae86b8ad&#34;&gt;加拿大学习许可&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;学习许可申请条件-飞出国:a274789a363a6b1dac89da47ae86b8ad&#34;&gt;学习许可申请条件 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;被加拿大指定的学习机构录取&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;足够的资金支撑学习、生活等支出&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;没有犯罪记录，需提供无犯罪证明&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;身体健康&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;承诺学习完成后会按时离境&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;豁免学习许可的情况-飞出国:a274789a363a6b1dac89da47ae86b8ad&#34;&gt;豁免学习许可的情况 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;学习6个月之内的短期课程&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;外国代表&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;外国军队&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;在加拿大注册的印第安人&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;学习许可申请流程-飞出国:a274789a363a6b1dac89da47ae86b8ad&#34;&gt;学习许可申请流程 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;可以在线申请，也可以纸质递交申请，以下为纸质递交的流程。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;准备好申请所需的材料；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;支付申请费： 150加币；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;递交申请： 中国申请人递交到就近的加拿大签证处理中心即可（&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/cvac-canada-visa-application-centre/2757&#34;&gt;CVAC&lt;/a&gt;）。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;学习许可申请处理周期-飞出国:a274789a363a6b1dac89da47ae86b8ad&#34;&gt;学习许可申请处理周期 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;北京使馆：7周&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;香港使馆：5周&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;上海使馆：7周&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;学习许可申请递交后 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;学习许可获批&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;申请人会收到确认信，当你抵达加拿大的时候提供此证明信&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;会签发一个临时居留签证（TRV - temporary resident visa）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;学习许可被拒&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;主要原因有：资金证明不足、体检不符合要求、学习目的不明确或无法证明会按时离境。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大学习许可延期:a274789a363a6b1dac89da47ae86b8ad&#34;&gt;加拿大学习许可延期&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;学习许可延期注意事项&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;加拿大学习许可延期，需要提前30天申请&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;17周岁以下的申请人，如果没有父母或监护人陪同，申请延期时还需要提供 Custodianship declaration (IMM 5646)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果打算出境旅游，并且在此期间，你的学习许可会过期的话，需要提前申请延期&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;延期后的时间不能超出护照有效期&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;学习许可到期后没有申请延期的，需要马上离境&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;学习许可延期获批后，需要向渥太华签证处理中心，递交临时签证申请&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;恢复身份（Restoring your status）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;失去身份后的90天内可以申请恢复身份。申请裁决期间，你可以继续留在加拿大，但是在申请获批之前不能学习。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;持有学习许可可以参加的工作类别:a274789a363a6b1dac89da47ae86b8ad&#34;&gt;持有学习许可可以参加的工作类别&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;校内工作-work-on-campus-飞出国:a274789a363a6b1dac89da47ae86b8ad&#34;&gt;校内工作（Work on campus） - 飞出国&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;申请人如果符合以下情况，不需要工作许可就可以直接在校内工作（work on campus at the institution）：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;全日制学生
&amp;gt;- a public post-secondary institution, such as a college or university, or a collège d’enseignement général et professionnel (CEGEP) in Quebec or&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; - a private post-secondary institution that operates under the same rules and regulations as a public institution, and receives at least 50 per cent of its financing for its overall operations from government grants (currently only private college-level educational institutions in Quebec qualify) or&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; - a Canadian private institution authorized by provincial statute to confer degrees and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;持有有效的学习许可&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;申请人一旦不满足上述要求，必须马上停止校内工作。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;校外工作-work-off-campus-飞出国:a274789a363a6b1dac89da47ae86b8ad&#34;&gt;校外工作（Work off campus） - 飞出国&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;自2014.6.1起，申请人如果满足下列条件，不需要工作许可就可以在校外工作：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;持有有效的学习许可&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;全日制学生&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;在指定学校（designated learning institution ）学习中学课程，或者在魁北克参加中学级别的职业教育课程&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;参加学术、职业或者专业的培训项目，学成后能获得学位、文凭或者证书（至少6个月）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;申请人一旦不满足上述要求，必须马上停止校外工作。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;毕业后工作-stay-in-canada-after-graduation-飞出国:a274789a363a6b1dac89da47ae86b8ad&#34;&gt;毕业后工作（Stay in Canada after graduation） - 飞出国&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;加拿大留学生毕业后想在加拿大工作，可以通过大学毕业生工作许可计划 (PGWPP - Post-Graduation Work Permit Program)申请。申请人之后可以用这些工作经验申请加拿大经验类移民（CEC - Canadian Experience Class）.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PGWPP下的工作签证有效期，根据之前的学习时间来定，不能超过学习时间，有效期最短8个月，最长3年。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;申请毕业后工作许可的要求 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;全日制学习，学习时间不低于8个月&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;学校要求：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a public post-secondary institution, such as a college, trade/technical school, university or CEGEP (in Quebec), or
a private post-secondary institution that operates under the same rules and regulations as public institutions, or
a private secondary or post-secondary institution (in Quebec) offering qualifying programs of 900 hours or longer leading to a diplôme d’études professionnelles (DEP) or an attestation de spécialisation professionnelle (ASP), or
a Canadian private institution authorized by provincial statute to confer degrees but only if you are enrolled in one of the programs of study leading to a degree as authorized by the province and not in all programs of study offered by the private institution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;收到学校证明你完成学业的书面确认书（a transcript or an official letter）的90天内申请&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;完成学习计划要求的课程并且成绩合格，符合获取学位、文凭或者证书的要求&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;持有有效的学习许可&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;学习时间和学习许可的有效期 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;毕业后工作许可的有效期不能比学习时间长。比如，学生学习的是4年的学位课程，学习许可的有效期只能为3年；学习的是8个月的证书课程，学习许可的有效期只能为8个月。如果申请人的学习课程&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;少于8个月：不能申请毕业后工作许可&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8个月至2年：学习许可有效期不能超过学习时间&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2年或2年以上：学习许可的有效期为3年&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;以下情况不能申请毕业后工作许可 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;所学课程的学习时间少于8个月&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;参加了加拿大外交、贸易和发展部（DFATD）成立的加拿大奖学金计划&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;参加了 DFATD 成立的加拿大政府奖励计划&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;收到过加拿大国际发展署提供的资金&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;参加了加拿大和智力两国的双边奖学金计划&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;参加了加拿大和中国的奖学金交换计划&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;参加了美洲国家组织奖学金计划&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;参加加拿大境内或境外的远程教育计划&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;过去曾经签发过毕业后工作许可&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;毕业后工作许可申请流程 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;准备申请材料&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;支付申请费：155加币&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;邮寄申请&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;帮助配偶在加拿大工作-飞出国:a274789a363a6b1dac89da47ae86b8ad&#34;&gt;帮助配偶在加拿大工作 - 飞出国&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;如果你符合下列要求，你的配偶也可以在加拿大工作：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;全日制学生&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a public post-secondary institution, such as a college or university, or a collège d’enseignement général et professionnel (CEGEP) in Quebec or&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a private post-secondary institution that operates under the same rules and regulations as a public institution, and receives at least 50 per cent of its financing for its overall operations from government grants (currently only private college-level educational institutions in Quebec qualify) or&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a Canadian private institution authorized by provincial statute to confer degrees and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;持有有效的学习许可&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;注意：配偶的工作许可有效期与你的有效期一样长。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;以上内容由飞出国论坛（&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com&#34;&gt;FCGvisa.com&lt;/a&gt;）独家整理完成，请尊重知识产权，转载请保留并注明出处。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>加拿大工作许可</title>
      <link>http://us.cgvisa.com/2805/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://us.cgvisa.com/2805/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;加拿大工作许可:9e79c97cb33ff519164dd3382db1e796&#34;&gt;加拿大工作许可&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大工作许可简介-work-permit-飞出国:9e79c97cb33ff519164dd3382db1e796&#34;&gt;加拿大工作许可简介（work permit） - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;加拿大工作许可(Work Permit)，是加拿大签发给海外劳工的一种许可，这个许可允许海外劳工在加拿大从事临时性工作。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;申请人的工作许可申请通过后，就会获得工作签证。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The visa officer will put it in your passport at the same time as they issue your authorization letter for a work permit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;申请人持有加拿大工作签证，入境加拿大的时候，加拿大边境官员会按照你提供的工作签证，在电脑系统中找出你的资料，现场打印给你工作许可，是一张单独的纸。也就是说，只有人到了加拿大，才能得到工作许可。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;工作许可允许你在加拿大从事工作许可上标注的工作职位，不能从事这个工作职位以外的工作。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;持有加拿大工作许可，只要加拿大工作签证没过期，就可以进行工作。工作许可期满或者中断，可以按照规定重新申请。如果你的工作签证到期而又没得到续签，你就必须要离开加拿大，不管你是否还持有有效的工作许可。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;取得加拿大工作签证是取得加拿大工作许可的前提，申请人只有在自己的国家拿到工作签证，才能在入境加拿大的时候，拿到工作许可。你在加拿大工作期间，如果你的工作签证到期，你需要按照规定续签的话，是否持有有效的工作许可，是一个重要因素。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;申请工作许可的基本要求-飞出国:9e79c97cb33ff519164dd3382db1e796&#34;&gt;申请工作许可的基本要求 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;保证在工作许可到期前离开加拿大；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;有足够的自己维持所以家庭成员在加拿大的开销和返程费用；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;没有犯罪记录；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;不会对加拿大安全造成危害；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;身体健康；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;不会为不合格的雇主工作（ ineligible employers,）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;自2011年4月1日起，一次或多次在加拿大的工作累计不超过4年；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;按官方要求提供相应的材料。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大工作许可申请方式-飞出国:9e79c97cb33ff519164dd3382db1e796&#34;&gt;加拿大工作许可申请方式 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;加拿大工作许可既可以在加拿大境外申请，可以在境内申请，后续会分别介绍。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大工作许可申请流程-飞出国:9e79c97cb33ff519164dd3382db1e796&#34;&gt;加拿大工作许可申请流程 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. 可以选择在线申请或者纸质申请；&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. 向雇主索取相关资料：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/lmia-lao-gong-shi-chang-ying-xiang-ping-gu-labour-market-impact-assessment-yu-jia-na-da-eejia-fen/2453&#34;&gt;LMIA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;工作offer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;教育和工作材料，证明申请人符合当前工作的要求&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. 提供所需的材料；&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. 支付申请费；&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;工作许可：155加币&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;三个或三个以上表演艺术家团体申请：465加币&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;开放工作许可：100加币&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. 递交申请。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;加拿大境内申请递交到 Case Processing Centre in Vegreville&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;初次申请递交到：&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; 6212-55th Avenue – Unit 555&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; Vegreville, AB&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; T9C 1X6&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;工作许可延期（同一雇主）递交到：
&amp;gt; 6212-55th Avenue – Unit 202&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; Vegreville, AB&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; T9C 1X6&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;从中国申请递交到就近的签证处理中心即可（&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/cvac-jia-na-da-qian-zheng-shen-qing-zhong-xin-canada-visa-application-centre/2757&#34;&gt;CVAC&lt;/a&gt;）。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大工作许可处理周期-飞出国:9e79c97cb33ff519164dd3382db1e796&#34;&gt;加拿大工作许可处理周期 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;北京使馆：3个月&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;香港使馆：6个月&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;上海使馆：3个月&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;不需要申请工签的公证类别:9e79c97cb33ff519164dd3382db1e796&#34;&gt;不需要申请工签的公证类别&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;从事以下工作的申请人不需要申请加拿大工签（work permit） - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;从 &lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/work-permit/2805&#34;&gt;加拿大工作许可综述（work permit）&lt;/a&gt; 继续讨论：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jobs that do not need a work permit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;运动员和教练员   Athletes and coaches&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;航空事故或事件调查员     Aviation accident or incident investigators&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;商务访问人员    Business visitors&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;民航督察  Civil aviation inspectors&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;教士    Clergy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;会议组织者 Convention organizers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;船员    Crew members&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;紧急服务提供商   Emergency service providers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;参加考试和考评人员     Examiners and evaluators&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;专家证人或调查员  Expert witnesses or investigators&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;外国代表的家庭成员     Family members of foreign representatives&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;外国政府官员    Foreign government officers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;外国代表  Foreign representatives&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;保健学生  Health care students&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;法官，裁判以及类似职位的官员    Judges, referees and similar officials&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;军事人员  Military personnel&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;新闻记者，电影和媒体人员  News reporters, film and media crews&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;表演艺术家 Performing artists&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;公众演讲人员    Public speakers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;在校外工作的学生  Students working off campus&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;在校内工作的学生  Students working on campus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大工作许可主要有以下类别-飞出国:9e79c97cb33ff519164dd3382db1e796&#34;&gt;加拿大工作许可主要有以下类别 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;外国工人 Foreign workers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;住家护理 Live-in caregivers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;商务人员 Business people&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;学生 Students&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;长期工 Permanent workers (immigrate to Canada)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;体验加拿大申请人 International Experience Canada applicants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大外国工人工作许可:9e79c97cb33ff519164dd3382db1e796&#34;&gt;加拿大外国工人工作许可&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;加拿大外国工人工作许可申请须知 - 飞出国：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;雇主需要申请LMIA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;雇主需要支付 employer compliance fee ，并且填写雇主offer表[IMM5802E]

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果申请人豁免LMIA，雇主需要在你申请工作许可前完成此步骤&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果申请开放工作许可，则不需要雇主提供材料

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果申请人豁免LMIA，并且获得了开放工作许可，你可以为不合格雇主（list of ineligible employers）之外的任意雇主工作&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;还需要申请访问签证&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;工作许可无法让申请人在加拿大长期居住，如果打算定居，需要申请永居签证&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;配偶或法律同居伴侣和未成年子女可以申请随行，也可以单独申请学习或工作许可&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;配偶或法律同居伴侣在加拿大工作 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;也需要申请工作许可，注意事项与主申请一样。但是配偶的工作许可期限要比主申的短。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;如果你符合下列情况，你的配偶或法律同居伴侣可以申请开放工作许可：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;被批准在加拿大工作6个月或6个月以上；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;从事NOC Skill Level 0，A或B的工作；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;注意：如果你持有开放工作许可，那么配偶在申请开放工作许可的时候，需要提供你的工作许可复印件以及：
- 你当前雇主的证明信，证明你从事的是NOC 0，A或B 的职业，或者工作offer或合同；以及
- 工资条复印件&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;随行子女想要在加拿大工作或学习 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;需要但是申请学习许可或者工作许可。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大住家护理工作许可-live-in-caregivers:9e79c97cb33ff519164dd3382db1e796&#34;&gt;加拿大住家护理工作许可 Live-in caregivers&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;住家护理指的是为小孩、老人或者残疾人提供看护服务的人员，必须居住在雇主家里。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;住家护理新政策 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;住家护理项目 (LCP - Live-in Caregiver Program (LCP) ) 于2014年11月30有一些新的改变：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果申请人当前不在加拿大从事住家护理工作，并且雇主的LMIA申请是在2014.11.30之后递交的，那么申请人只能申请常规的工作许可&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果申请人当前不在加拿大从事住家护理工作，并且雇主的LMIA申请是在2014.11.30或者之前递交的，申请人可以申请LCP工作许可&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果申请人已经持有住家护理工作许可，打算延期或者更换雇主，申请人可以申请LCP许可&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果申请人不想住在雇主家里，申请人需要放弃住家护理工作

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;需要重新申请常规工作许可。当前或者未来的雇主需要重新申请LMIA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The work you do on a live-out basis may count towards the work requirement in order to apply through either the Caring for Children or Caring for People with High Medical Needs pathway.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;住家护理申请要求 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;雇主申请LMIA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;与雇主签订的劳动合同&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;学历等同于加拿大高中学历&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;过去3年中，至少6个月的相关的培训，或者至少1年全职带薪的相关工作经验（其中有6个月为同一雇主工作）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;良好的英语或法语沟通能力&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LCP 工作许可申请流程 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. 雇主在2014.11.30之前递交了LMIA申请，并且获得了Positive 的结果。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. 与雇主签证合同。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;递交工作许可申请的时候，需要附上LMIA和合同的复印件。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. 申请工作许可&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;可以在线申请或纸质申请。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;在线申请能力测试入口&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cic.gc.ca/ctc-vac/getting-started.asp&#34;&gt;http://www.cic.gc.ca/ctc-vac/getting-started.asp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;纸质申请步骤&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;准备申请材料&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;支付申请费&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;递交申请&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大学生工作许可:9e79c97cb33ff519164dd3382db1e796&#34;&gt;加拿大学生工作许可&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;加拿大留学生也可以在加拿大工作，主要有以下5种类型：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;校内工作（Work on campus）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;校外工作（Work off campus）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;实习生工作（Work as a co-op or intern）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;毕业后工作（Stay in Canada after graduation）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;帮助配偶工作（Help your spouse or common-law partner find work）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大工作许可延期:9e79c97cb33ff519164dd3382db1e796&#34;&gt;加拿大工作许可延期&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;加拿大工作许可到期后，如果还想继续留在加拿大，需要在工作许可到期前30天申请延期。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;外国工人申请工作许可延期（Foreign workers） - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;申请人如果发生以下情况，并且打算继续留在加拿大境内，需要申请工作许可延期：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;工作延期或者更换工作内容

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;需要申请工作许可延期或者改变原来工作许可上的&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;条款。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;更换工作

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;需要申请新的工作许可。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;打算在加拿大长期定居

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;工作许可到期后，如果打算长期定居加拿大，需要申请移民。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;离开加拿大一段时间，再回来

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;申请人必须先获得工作许可延期，然后离境，延期的最长期限不超过4年。如有特别紧急的状况，申请人可以在延期获批前离境。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;住家护理申请工作许可延期（Live-in caregivers） - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;申请人如果发生以下情况，并且打算继续留在加拿大境内，需要申请工作许可延期：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;更换工作&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;辞职或者失业后需要申请新工作&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;打算长期定居并且有足够的工作经验后可以申请永居移民&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;永久居民申请人申请工作许可延期（Permanent resident applicants） - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;适用人群：当前已经递交了联邦技术移民（FSW）、加拿大经验类移民（CEC）、省提名移民（PNP）或者技工移民（FST）的申请人，如果他们的工作许可即将过期，他们可以申请开放工作许可。申请要求：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;当前在加拿大境内&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;当前持有的有效的工作许可在4个月内到期&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;收到CIC确认移民申请通过初审
&amp;gt; Have received confirmation from CIC that your permanent resident application is eligible under one of the four economic classes (FSWP, CEC, PNP and FSTP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大工作许可的材料清单-中国申请人:9e79c97cb33ff519164dd3382db1e796&#34;&gt;加拿大工作许可的材料清单（中国申请人）&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;申请表格及材料&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IMM1295] - 加拿大境外工作许可申请表&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IMM5645] - 家庭信息表，如适用&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IMM5257] - TRV申请表，如适用&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IMM5409] - 同居伴侣法定声明，如适用&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IMM5476] - 代理表，如适用&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;豁免LMIA的工作offer以及支付收据（需要雇主提供给你）Offer of Employment to a Foreign National Exempt from a Labour Market Impact Assessment (LMIA) (IMM 5802) with proof of payment by the employer (receipt number). Your employer should provide it to you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LMIA的复印件（如适用），以及未来雇主提供的offer的复印件&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果你请求豁免LMIA，需要提供省政府提名函复印件。如果提名函已过期，需要提供 CIC在提名函过期之前收到了永居申请的确认信的复印件。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;满足工作要求的证明文件&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果在魁北克工作，需要提供CAQ&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;费用支付&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;提供护照原件（需要TRV）(中国申请人需要);或者护照首页复印件（不需要TRV）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2张移民照片，背面写上名字和出生日期

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;备注：如果申请人被要求指纹和照片，无需提供纸质照片&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;当前移民文件的复印件，如使用（如：学习许可、工作许可或临时居留许可）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;资金证明&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;签证中心的要求的额外材料&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;可选：已在指定医院完成体检的证明&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;以上内容由飞出国论坛（&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com&#34;&gt;FCGvisa.com&lt;/a&gt;）独家整理完成，请尊重知识产权，转载请保留并注明出处。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>加拿大父母、祖父母团聚移民 pgp</title>
      <link>http://us.cgvisa.com/2598/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://us.cgvisa.com/2598/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;加拿大家庭团聚移民-父母-祖父母团聚-sponsor-your-parents-and-grandparents-飞出国&#34;&gt;加拿大家庭团聚移民-父母、祖父母团聚(Sponsor your parents and grandparents) - 飞出国&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大父母-祖父母团聚签证担保人的要求-飞出国-pgp&#34;&gt;加拿大父母、祖父母团聚签证担保人的要求（飞出国 PGP）&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;担保人是加拿大公民或者加拿大永久居民；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;担保人当前必须居住在加拿大境内；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;担保人年满18周岁；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;签署书面的担保协议，承诺将会为申请人以及随行人员提供任何需要的财政援助，期限为自父母、祖父母获签起的10年之内；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么条件的人不可以担保父母、祖父母申请团聚移民（飞出国 PGP）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;对于曾经担保过的亲属，未能提供担保协议中承诺的财政支持；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;未履行法院判决，如按规定支付赡养费和子女抚养费等；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;因为除了残疾以外的其他原因，而获得过政府财政援助；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;有过暴力犯罪经历；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;未偿还移民贷款-由于延期支付或者忘记支付；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;服刑期间；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;宣布破产还未受理完成的。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果担保人过去担保过的亲属，有移民后向政府寻求过经济援助的，那么你将不能再担保其他人。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;pgp-加拿大父母-祖父母团聚签证申请流程-飞出国&#34;&gt;PGP 加拿大父母、祖父母团聚签证申请流程 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. 填写相关的 &lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/jia-na-da-fu-mu-zu-fu-mu-jia-ting-tuan-ju-yi-min-cai-liao-qing-dan/2599&#34;&gt;PGP 申请表格及准备清单要求的材料&lt;/a&gt; - 飞出国；&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. PGP 支付申请费 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;担保申请：75加币（每个申请）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;主申（父母或祖父母）：475加币；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;主申19周岁以下的未婚子女：150加币；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;主申19周岁以上的未婚子女或者19周岁以下的已婚子女：550加币；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;支付方式：信用卡，或者认可的支票；&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. PGP 递交申请 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;材料准备齐全后，寄往：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CPC Mississauga&lt;br /&gt;
P.O. Box 6100, Station A&lt;br /&gt;
Mississauga, ON&lt;br /&gt;
L5A 4H4&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;pgp-加拿大父母-祖父母团聚签证申请周期-2015-4-21更新-飞出国&#34;&gt;PGP 加拿大父母、祖父母团聚签证申请周期（2015.4.21更新） - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;对担保人的评估：48个月(2011.4.30之前递交 的申请)；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;对申请人的评估：北京使馆67个月；香港使馆28个月。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;虽然加拿大 CIC 一直打算加快父母类团聚移民的速度，但因为申请人多，配额少，效果不会太明显，详见 &lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/jia-na-da-fu-mu-he-zu-fu-mu-tuan-ju-yi-min-shen-qing-chu-li-ti-su/2575&#34;&gt;PGP 加拿大父母和祖父母团聚移民申请处理提速计划&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;加拿大父母、祖父母家庭团聚移民官方链接:&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cic.gc.ca/english/immigrate/sponsor/parents.asp&#34;&gt;PGP 父母、祖父母团聚&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大父母-祖父母家庭团聚移民材料清单-checklist-飞出国&#34;&gt;加拿大父母、祖父母家庭团聚移民材料清单（Checklist） - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;加拿大父母、祖父母家庭团聚移民申请表格 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/imm-1334e/4538&#34;&gt;IMM1344E&lt;/a&gt;  - 担保人协议;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/imm5768e/4541&#34;&gt;IMM5768E&lt;/a&gt;  - 担保人财政能力评估表；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cic.gc.ca/english/pdf/kits/forms/IMM5409E.pdf&#34;&gt;IMM5409E&lt;/a&gt;  - 同居伴侣法定声明（如果联合担保人是担保人的法律同居伴侣）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/2d-imm0008enu-2d/2454&#34;&gt;IMM0008ENU_2D&lt;/a&gt;  - 基本信息表&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cic.gc.ca/english/pdf/kits/forms/IMM0008DEPENU.pdf&#34;&gt;IMM0008DEPENU&lt;/a&gt;  -    如果家庭成员达到5个需要填写；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/5669-imm5669e/2502&#34;&gt;IMM5669E&lt;/a&gt;  - 教育工作履历表；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/5406-imm5406e/2496&#34;&gt;IMM5406E&lt;/a&gt;  -  家庭成员表；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/imm5476e-guide-5561-instructions-use-of-a-representative/4235&#34;&gt;IMM5476E&lt;/a&gt; - 代理表（如适用）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/imm-5770e/4563&#34;&gt;IMM5770E&lt;/a&gt;  - 费用支付表&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;加拿大父母、祖父母家庭团聚移民申请材料 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;以下任一材料的复印件： 枫叶卡双面复印，或者移民纸（IMM 1000），或者永居身份确认文件(IMM 5292 或 IMM 5688)；或者加拿大公民证书（双面复印）；或者加拿大出生证明；或者加拿大护照首页；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果配偶是联合担保人，需要提供结婚证书复印件；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果配偶是联合担保人，也需要提供 1 中的材料；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;担保人与申请人关系证明文件：担保人出生证明复印件；如果担保父母的父母，需要提供父母的出生证明复印件；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;提供最近3年税务年度的税单原件（打印即可）。可以从加拿大税务局（CRA）免费获取。如果不能提供，需要提供单独的解释说明信；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;申请人和随行人员护照首页复印件；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;主申和随行受供养配偶的：结婚证书或者联合声明（IMM 5409表）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;主申和随行受供养子女的关系证明：所有随行子女的出生证明。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;加拿大父母、祖父母家庭团聚移民官方材料清单： &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cic.gc.ca/english/pdf/kits/forms/IMM5771E.PDF&#34;&gt;http://www.cic.gc.ca/english/pdf/kits/forms/IMM5771E.PDF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;以上内容由飞出国论坛（&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com&#34;&gt;FCGvisa.com&lt;/a&gt;）独家整理完成，请尊重知识产权，转载请保留并注明出处。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>加拿大父母和祖父母超级签证pgs</title>
      <link>http://us.cgvisa.com/2690/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://us.cgvisa.com/2690/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;加拿大父母和祖父母超级签证-super-visa-pgs-飞出国:84cc934fd4660fc9abed647b3e5898e5&#34;&gt;加拿大父母和祖父母超级签证 Super Visa PGS  - 飞出国&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;为了缓解父母和祖父母家庭团聚移民申请的积压，2011年加拿大移民部新开设了父母和祖父母超级签证 PGS（parent and grandparent super visa），超级签证的有效期为10年，它允许申请人一次最多可以在加拿大境内逗留2年。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;super-visa-加拿大父母和祖父母超级签证对申请人的要求-飞出国:84cc934fd4660fc9abed647b3e5898e5&#34;&gt;Super Visa 加拿大父母和祖父母超级签证对申请人的要求 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;申请人的子女或孙子孙女是加拿大公民或者永久居民；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;申请中不能包含除申请人的配偶和同居伴侣之外的其他随行人员；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;申请人的子女或孙子孙女满足最低收入要求；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//disfly.s3.amazonaws.com/original/2X/3/39b1b3a3956058c71771009cf341e28d72797e00.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;申请人的子女或孙子孙女承诺为申请人提供财政援助的书面声明；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;申请人已经够买了至少1年的加拿大医疗保险；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;申请人通过体检；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;申请人不能是加拿大拒绝入境的人士，例如有犯罪纪录。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;super-visa-加拿大父母和祖父母超级签证申请方式-飞出国:84cc934fd4660fc9abed647b3e5898e5&#34;&gt;Super Visa 加拿大父母和祖父母超级签证申请方式 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;在线申请；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;纸质申请。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;加拿大超级签证材料清单-飞出国:84cc934fd4660fc9abed647b3e5898e5&#34;&gt;加拿大超级签证材料清单 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note/注意: All Documents in Chinese must be accompanied by an English or French translation.所有中文文件必须附有英文或法文的翻译件。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Completed “Application for a Temporary Resident Visa” (IMM 5257). An Application form is required for each applicant, including each accompanying child.
填写完整的“临时居民访问签证申请表 (IMM5257）”。每位申请人及每位随行子女均需一份单独的申请表格。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Completed “Family Information” form (IMM 5645) for you and each accompanying family member aged 18 years old and above, completed in English or French AND Chinese.
申请人及每位年满  18 周岁及以上的随行家庭成员完整填写“家庭信息表”（IMM5645），请使用中英文或中法文填写&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two  (2) identical   photos  of  the applicant   and each accompanying family member, colour or black and white taken against a plain white or light coloured background within the last 6 months. The frame size is 35mm X 45mm. On the back of one photo in each set, write the name in pinyin and date of birth (day/month/year) of the person appearing in the photo.
申请人及每位随行的家庭成员每人需递交两张相同的在最近六个月内拍摄的彩色或黑白照片，背景为纯白色或浅色。相片外框大小为 35 毫米 X 45 毫米。每张照片后以拼音注明此    人的姓名及出生日期（日/月/年）。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A  valid  passport  for  the  applicant  and  each  accompanying family member. There must be one completely blank page other than the last page, available in each passport and each passport must be valid for at least six (6) months prior to travel
申请人及每位随行的家庭成员的有效护照。每本护照须包含除最后一页外的至少一整页空白页、且护照必须在行程前至少六个月有效。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two  (2)  self-addressed  adhesive  labels  with  the  applicant’s current address in Chinese characters (no envelope). 两份用中文写有申请人现住址的粘性贴纸 (无需信封)。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The correct application processing fee paid in cash. Fee is non- refundable.
以现金支付正确的申请受理费。受理费不予退还。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Use of a Representative” form (IMM5476E) if someone has assisted you in making this application.
如有第三方人士帮助你准备此次申请，请填写代理人信息表（IMM5476E）。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;For children less than 18 years old, Parental Letter of Consent from your non-accompanying parent(s) authorizing your travel. This letter should contain the dates of travel and your parent(s)’ contact information.
18 岁以下的申请人需有其未随行父/母出具的同意其旅行的父母同意函，此函应包含申请人旅行日期及其父母联系方式等 信息。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proof of relationship with the inviter in Canada (e.g. copy of birth certificate, copy of relationship certificate). 与加拿大邀请人关系的证明(如出生证复印件、关系证明复印件)。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A   written   and   signed   invitation   letter   promising   financial support for the duration of your visit.
一份签字的承诺为申请人的逗留访问提供财政支持的书面邀请信。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A list showing the number of people in inviter’s household.
邀请人居所内的人员详单。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A copy of the inviter’s citizenship or immigration status document (e.g. Permanent Resident Card – please copy both sides).
邀请人的公民或移民身份文件的复印件（如永久居民卡 – 请复印双面)。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proof of inviter’s ability to provide promised financial support in the form of independent, third-party documentation from a Canadian source which is reliable or easily verifiable. For example, but not limited to: Canada Revenue Agency Notice of Assessments [NOA], employment letters showing salary, pay stubs, banks statements, Statements of Remuneration Paid or financial statements prepared by a licensed professional.
邀请人有能力提供所承诺财政支持的证明，须为来自于加拿大的独立第三方性质的文件、可靠且易核实。例如但不局限 于：加拿大税务总局出具的税单(NOA)，显示收入情况的雇 佣证明信，工资单，银行对账单，执业专业人士出具的薪酬 支付报表或财务报表。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Satisfactory evidence of private medical insurance from a Canadian insurance company, valid for  a  minimum period  of one year from the date of entry which:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;covers  the  applicant  for  health  care,  hospitalization  and repatriation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;provides a minimum of $100,000 coverage; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;is valid for each entry to Canada and available for review by the examining officer upon request&lt;br /&gt;
自入境之日起至少一年内有效的来自于加拿大保险公司的个
人医疗保险的充分证明:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;涵盖申请人的医疗费用、住院费用和医疗转运费用;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;提供至少十万加元的保险；并且&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;每次入加均有效，在评估官员需要时可供审查&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you intend to travel to the United States during your visit to Canada, you do not need a multiple -entry visa in order to re-enter Canada directly from the United States during the period  for  which  you  were  originally admitted to Canada.
如果申请人想在访问加拿大期间前往美国，在加拿大合法停留期限之内从美国再次进入加拿大不需要一个多次入境签证。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that the processing fee is non-refundable for any application that is withdrawn or refused.
请注意任何撤销或被拒签的申请受理费用都不予退还。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;以上内容由飞出国论坛（&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com&#34;&gt;FCGvisa.com&lt;/a&gt;）独家整理完成，请尊重知识产权，转载请保留并注明出处。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>加拿大配偶、同居伴侣和子女团聚移民</title>
      <link>http://us.cgvisa.com/2557/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://us.cgvisa.com/2557/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;加拿大配偶-同居伴侣和子女团聚移民&#34;&gt;加拿大配偶、同居伴侣和子女团聚移民&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;飞出国注&lt;/strong&gt;：自2014.8.1开始，CIC修改了对受供养子女（dependent child）的年龄定义，由之前的22周岁以下，改为了19周岁以下。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;如果你是加拿大公民或者加拿大永久居民，那么你可以担保你的配偶、同居伴侣和子女移民加拿大。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;sclpc-配偶子女团聚签证担保人的要求-飞出国&#34;&gt;SCLPC 配偶子女团聚签证担保人的要求（飞出国）&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;担保人必须是加拿大公民或定居在加拿大的永久居民。如果是公民，申请时可以不居住在加拿大境内，但是如果是加拿大永居的话，必须是定居在加拿大才能提供担保。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;担保人的年龄要在18周岁以上；&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;书面文件承诺给申请人提供经济支持：配偶和同居伴侣需要提供3年；受供养子女提供10年或者持续到25岁，已先到的为准（比如申请人当前17岁，那么需要提供到25岁，如果当前申请人13岁，只需提供到23岁即可）；&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果担保人是通过申请配偶或者同居伴侣担保而移民的，成为加拿大永居的时间满5年，才能担保配偶或同居伴侣移民(以上条款只适用于2012年3月2号之后成为永居的担保人，在此之前的永居不受影响。)，但是可以担保其他家庭成员移民，比如受供养子女，父母等。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么条件的人不可以做 SCLPC 配偶子女团聚签证担保人（飞出国）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;不符合担保协议中的相关条款；&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;没有按法庭判决支付赡养费和子女抚养费的；&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;除身体残疾以外的其他原因而申请政府财政援助的；&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;因为以下原因被判有罪的：性侵、暴力、攻击亲属导致肉体伤害、试图或者威胁性犯罪行为（要看犯罪类型、发生的时间和是否已经暂停记录）；&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;担保人是通过申请配偶或者同居伴侣担保而移民的，且成为加拿大永居的时间不满5年的；&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;由于延期支付或者忘记支付，未偿还移民贷款；&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;正在服刑人员；&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;宣布破产还未受理完成的；&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果担保人过去担保过的亲属，有移民后向政府寻求过经济援助的，那么你将不能再担保其他人。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么条件的人不可以申请 SCLPC 配偶团聚（飞出国）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;年龄不满16周岁；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;在你们婚姻期间，申请人或者担保人与另外的人结婚；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;分居超过1年，并且其中一方与第三人成为同居伴侣关系；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;担保人申请永居时，文件中没有体现配偶的信息（当时已结婚的话）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;担保人曾经担保过配偶移民，并且那个配偶获得永居身份不满3年（如果是2012.3.2之后担保的配偶移民，则需要满足5年才可以）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;sclpc-配偶子女团聚签证的申请流程-飞出国&#34;&gt;SCLPC 配偶子女团聚签证的申请流程 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. 填写相关的申请表格及准备清单要求的材料 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. SCLPC 支付申请费 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;申请费用：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;担保申请：75加币（每个申请）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;主申（配偶）：475加币；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;19周岁以下的主申请（未婚子女）：75加币；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;财政无法自足的已满19周岁主申请（子女）：475加币；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;19周岁以下的随行子女（未婚）：150加币；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;财政无法自足的已满19周岁的随行子女：475加币；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;可选的支付方式：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;所有申请人都可以在线支付（建议）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果在加拿大境内申请，还可以通过银行支付；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果在加拿大境外，还可以通过邮政汇票和银行汇票支付。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;登录费（为减少处理时间，建议与申请费一起支付）：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;主申（配偶）：490加币&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. SCLPC 提交申请 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1和2 完成后，将所有材料寄往签证处理中心（Case Processing Centre in Mississauga, Ontario）.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;加拿大境外配偶、同居伴侣和子女团聚，将申请材料寄往：
&amp;gt; CPC Mississauga&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; P.O. Box 3000, Station A&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; Mississauga, ON&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;gt; L5A 4N6&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;当前居住在加拿大境内的配偶和同居伴侣，将申请材料寄往：
&amp;gt; CPC-Mississauga
&amp;gt; P.O. Box 5040, Station B
&amp;gt; Mississauga, ON
&amp;gt; L5A 3A4&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;sclpc-配偶子女团聚签证的处理周期-2015-4-21更新-飞出国&#34;&gt;SCLPC 配偶子女团聚签证的处理周期（2015.4.21更新） - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;加拿大境外申请&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;对担保人的评估：62天（适用于2015.2.19之后收到的申请）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;对被担保人的评估：周期取决于不同的使馆，北京使馆和香港使馆都是9个月&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;加拿大境内申请&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;对担保人的评估：17个月（适用于2013.11.13之后收到的申请）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;对被担保人的评估:10个月&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;sclpc-加拿大配偶子女团聚签证申请材料清单-加拿大境内申请imm5443e-checklist-飞出国&#34;&gt;SCLPC 加拿大配偶子女团聚签证申请材料清单 - 加拿大境内申请IMM5443E(Checklist) - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. SCLPC 申请表格 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;申请人填写的表格：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/2d-imm0008enu-2d/2454&#34;&gt;IMM0008ENU_2D&lt;/a&gt; 基本信息表&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cic.gc.ca/english/pdf/kits/forms/IMM0008DEPENU.pdf&#34;&gt;IMM0008DEPENU&lt;/a&gt;  如果家庭成员达到5个需要填写&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/5406-imm5406e/2496&#34;&gt;IMM5406E&lt;/a&gt;  家庭成员表&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/5669-imm5669e/2502&#34;&gt;IMM5669E&lt;/a&gt;  教育工作履历表&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/immm5285e-spouse-common-law-questionnaire/4586&#34;&gt;IMM5285E&lt;/a&gt;  夫妻或者同居关系调查表&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;担保人填写的表格：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/imm-1344e-application-to-sponsor-sponsorship-agreement-and-undertaking/4538&#34;&gt;IMM1344E&lt;/a&gt; - 担保人和申请人协议&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/imm5481e-sponsorship-evaluation/4569&#34;&gt;IMM5481E&lt;/a&gt; - 担保能力评估表，或者[IMM1283] - 财政评估表&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;担保人和申请人都需要填写的表格：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/imm5476e-guide-5561-instructions-use-of-a-representative/4235&#34;&gt;IMM5476E&lt;/a&gt; - 代理表（如适用）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IMM5443E][5443]  - 本清单&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. SCLPC 申请需要下面材料的复印件（有特殊要求提供原件的除外）- 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PHOTOCOPIES (OR ORIGINALS WHEN INDICATED) OF THE FOLLOWING ITEMS(Photocopies do not need to be certified. Do not send original documents unless specified as they will not be returned)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;申请人以及其未成年子女需要提供的文件：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;护照首页；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;证明其在加拿大身份的文件（如：访问签证、学习或工作许可，包括已经失去身份的材料也需要提供），如有过；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;美国绿卡双面复印，如有；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;申请人的出生证明；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;随行子女的出生证明或者加拿大公民证书；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;监护证明文件（离异过）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果有收养的子女还需要提供收养文件；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;无犯罪证明原件；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;可选：如果已经预先在体检医院做了体检的话，需要提供体检结果，也可以等收到通知后再去体检。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the applicant and his or her dependent children&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passport pages clearly showing your passport number, name, date of birth, passport issue/expiry dates and stamp made by a Canadian authority showing your most recent entry into Canada&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Indication of status in Canada (e.g. visitor visa, study permit or work permit, temporary resident permit, including out of status documentation)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Both sides of United States Alien Registration card (Green Card), if applicable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Birth certificate for you&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Birth certificate or Canadian citizenship certificate for any dependent children&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Custody papers for your children from a previous relationship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adoption papers for your dependent children who were adopted&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Original police certificates (Refer to Appendix A)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optional: proof of completion of the upfront medical examination from the Panel Physician (if you do not hold a valid medical Report, instructions will be given to you when you receive your notice of eligibility)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;担保人需要提供的文件（提供以下任一文件的复印件即可）：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;移民纸或者能证明永居身份的文件；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;加拿大出生公证；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;加拿大公民证书或公民卡（双面复印）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;枫叶卡双面复印；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;国外出生注册证书双面复印；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;加拿大护照首页。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the sponsor: Proof of permanent resident status or Canadian citizenship
Photocopy of one of the following items:
- Record of Landing (IMM 1000) or Confirmation of Permanent Residence document (IMM 5292 or IMM 5688)
- Canadian birth certificate
- Canadian Citizenship Certificate or card (both sides)
- Both sides of your permanent resident card
- Both sides of your certificate of registration of birth abroad
- Pages from your Canadian passport or travel document showing the passport or travel document number, date of issue and expiration, your photo and your name, surname, place and date of birth&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;担保人和申请人都需要提供的 - 飞出国 SCLPC ：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;结婚证复印件；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果有婚史的话，需要提供离婚、取消婚姻、分居或前配偶死亡证书；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;法律同居伴侣关系（common-law relationship）证明文件（e.g., evidence of joint bank, trust, credit union or charge card accounts; jointly signed residential lease, mortgage or purchase agreement; statutory declarations of individuals with personal knowledge that your relationship is genuine and continuing）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;结婚典礼照片（如有）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;夫妻关系（conjugal relationship）证明（e.g., commitment, housing and financial arrangements, social activities, attitudes and mindsets towards your relationship）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;与前同居伴侣断绝关系的证明材料（如有）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;注意：如果申请人和担保人是common-law or conjugal partners，还需要提供与前伴侣关系的证明。如果申请人和担保人的伴侣关系少于或等于2年，并且没有子女，申请通过后，申请人会收到有条件的永居身份。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For both of you:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photocopy of marriage certificate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photocopy of divorce, annulment, separation or death certificates, if either of you were previously married&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proof of your common-law relationship (e.g., evidence of joint bank, trust, credit union or charge card accounts; jointly signed residential lease, mortgage or purchase agreement; statutory declarations of individuals with personal knowledge that your relationship is genuine and continuing)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photographs of the marriage or common-law relationship ceremony, if applicable (photocopies are acceptable; originals will not be returned)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proof of your conjugal relationship (e.g., commitment, housing and financial arrangements, social activities, attitudes and mindsets towards your relationship)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Declaration of severance of common-law relationship Note: The sponsor and the applicant who are common-law or conjugal partners must provide historical evidence of their ongoing relationship. If they are in a relationship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. 移民照片 - 飞出国 SCLPC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;申请人和子女各提供2张移民照片&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. 担保人收入证明文件 - 飞出国 SCLPC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1）需要附上以下文件：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;提供最近一个税务年度的税单和工资条（打印即可）。可以从加拿大税务局（CRA）免费获取。如果不能提供，需要提供单独的解释说明信；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果近12个月内收到过社会救助/福利，并且这些救助情况没有在T5007表中列出的话，需要提供：福利发放的收据复印件；其他的政府补偿的收据复印件；&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;如果当前在职，需要提供雇主推荐信原件&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An original Option C printout of your last Notice of Assessment for the most recent taxation year along with printouts of all income slips (e.g. T4, T4E, T5 and T5007). To obtain these printouts free-of-charge from the Canada Revenue Agency, call 1 800 959-8281. If you do not provide this printout, provide an explanation on a separate sheet of paper.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you received social assistance/welfare in the last 12 months that is not listed on the computer printout of the T5007, include:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photocopy of receipt from welfare&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photocopy of receipt from any other government payment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you are employed, an original of a letter from your current employer stating your period of employment, salary, and regular hours per week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2）如果你担保的配偶的未成年子女有未成年子女的话，需要完成以下部分：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;如果你无法提供近1年的税单；或者 能提供近1年的税单，但是总收入不满足最低收入标准，需要提供以下收入证明材料：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are sponsoring a spouse or common-law partner with dependent children who have dependent children of their own and either of these situations applies to you, complete this section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are not producing an original Option C printout of your last Notice of Assessment for the most recent year; OR&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are producing an original Option C printout of your last Notice of Assessment for the most recent year, but the total income reported on your printout is less than the minimum necessary income, then provide the documents listed below as proof of your income.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a. Evidence of employment income (pay stubs and photocopy of your most recent T1 - Individual Income Tax Return) over the 12 months preceding the date of your sponsorship application, if you are employed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;b. Evidence of self-employment income (statement of business activities from your accountant) over the 12 months preceding the date of your sponsorship application, if you are the sole owner of or partner in an unincorporated business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;c. Evidence of interest income (bank statement showing rate of interest, deposit amount and length of time deposit held), over the 12 months preceding the date of your sponsorship application, if you received interest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;d. Evidence of income received over the 12 months preceding the date of your sponsorship application, if you received;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;investment income (e.g., dividends),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;rental income (e.g., statement of real estate rentals),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;pension income,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;special benefits income (e.g., certificate delivered by Employment and Social Development Canada (ESDC) ( confirming payment maternity, parental of sickness benefits),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;other income (give details below).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. 申请费 PROCESSING FEES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copy 2 of the Receipt form that has been stamped by a financial institution showing the amount paid or Internet receipt. (No other form of payment is acceptable)：____&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have addressed the envelope with the correct postage to: CPC-M, PO Box 5040 STN B, Mississauga, ON, L5A 3A4&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;加拿大配偶和子女团聚移民 - 加拿大境内申请官方材料清单： &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cic.gc.ca/english/pdf/kits/forms/IMM5443E.pdf&#34;&gt;http://www.cic.gc.ca/english/pdf/kits/forms/IMM5443E.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;sclpc-加拿大配偶子女团聚签证申请材料清单-加拿大境外申请-imm5491e-document-checklist-sponsor-飞出国&#34;&gt;SCLPC 加拿大配偶子女团聚签证申请材料清单 - 加拿大境外申请 IMM5491E(DOCUMENT CHECKLIST - SPONSOR) - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.  SCLPC 申请表格（提供原件） - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;担保人填写的表格：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/imm-1344e-application-to-sponsor-sponsorship-agreement-and-undertaking/4538&#34;&gt;IMM1344E&lt;/a&gt; - 担保人和申请人协议；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/imm5481e-sponsorship-evaluation/4569&#34;&gt;IMM5481E&lt;/a&gt; - 担保能力评估表；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/imm5476e-guide-5561-instructions-use-of-a-representative/4235&#34;&gt;IMM5476E&lt;/a&gt;- 代理表（如适用）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;费用支付证明&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/statutory-declaration-of-common-law-union/4567&#34;&gt;IMM5409E&lt;/a&gt; - 法律同居伴侣联合担保法定声明（如果联合担保人是担保人的法律同居伴侣）；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/imm5540e-sponsor-questionnaire/4578&#34;&gt;IMM5540E&lt;/a&gt; - 担保人调查表；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;被担保人（申请人）及其家庭成员填写的表格：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7.&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/2d-imm0008enu-2d/2454&#34;&gt;IMM0008ENU_2D&lt;/a&gt;  - 基本信息表；&lt;br /&gt;
8.&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cic.gc.ca/english/pdf/kits/forms/IMM0008DEPENU.pdf&#34;&gt;IMM0008DEPENU&lt;/a&gt;  - 如果家庭成员达到5个需要填写 ；
9. &lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/5669-imm5669e/2502&#34;&gt;IMM5669E&lt;/a&gt;  - 教育工作履历表；
10. &lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/immm5490e-sponsored-spouse-partner-questionnaire/4585&#34;&gt;IMM5490E&lt;/a&gt;  - 夫妻或者同居关系调查表；
11. &lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/5406-imm5406e/2496&#34;&gt;IMM5406E&lt;/a&gt;  - 家庭成员信息表；&lt;br /&gt;
12. &lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/imm5476e-guide-5561-instructions-use-of-a-representative/4235&#34;&gt;IMM5476E&lt;/a&gt; - 代理表（如适用）。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;双方都需要填写：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IMM5491E][5491]  - 本清单&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.SCLPC 申请材料复印件（特殊要求的除外）- 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;担保人需要提供的文件：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13.身份文件：枫叶卡双面复印，或者移民纸（IMM 1000），或者永居身份确认文件(IMM 5292 或 IMM 5688)；或者加拿大公民证书（双面复印）；或者加拿大出生证明；或者加拿大护照；&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;14.结婚证，如果配偶是联名担保人的话；&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;15.如果配偶或同居伴侣是联名担保人，还需要提供其身份文件（参考第13项）；&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;16.如果有过婚史或者同居伴侣，需提供以下文件的复印件：分居证明；离婚证明；婚姻取消证明；前配偶死亡证书（如有）；断绝关系声明等；&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;17.提供最近一个税务年度的税单原件（打印即可）可以从加拿大税务局（CRA）免费获取。如果不能提供，需要提供单独的解释说明信（An original &amp;ldquo;Option C Printout&amp;rdquo; of your and your co-signer&amp;rsquo;s last Notice of Assessment for the most recent taxation year.To obtain this printout free-of-charge from the Canada Revenue Agency, call 1 800 959-8281. If you do not provide this printout, provide an explanation on a separate sheet of paper.）；&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;18.雇主推荐信和/或收入证明；&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proof of employment&lt;/strong&gt;
If you are employed, provide an original letter from your current employer stating your period of employment, salary, and regular hours per week. If you have a co-signer who is employed, include a similar letter from his or her employer.
&lt;strong&gt;AND/OR&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;strong&gt;Proof of income&lt;/strong&gt;
 For the 12 months preceding the date of your sponsorship, if you and, if applicable, your co-signer:&lt;br /&gt;
    -   are the sole owners of, or partners in an unincorporated business, provide evidence of self-employment income (statement of business activities).
    -  received interest on income earned, provide evidence of interest income (bank statement showing rate of interest, deposit amount and length of time deposit held).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;19.满足加拿大最低收入证明&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you must meet the minimum necessary income requirement and you and, if applicable, your co-signer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;are not producing an original Option-C printout of your last Notice of Assessment for the most recent year or&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;are producing an original Option-C printout of your last Notice of Assessment for the most recent year, but the total income reported on your and your co-signer&amp;rsquo;s printout is less than the mininum necessary income, provide a photocopy of the following documents

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a. Evidence of employment income (pay stubs) over the 12 months preceding the date of your sponsorship application, if you and your co-signer are employed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;b. Evidence of self-employment income (statement of business activities) over the 12 months preceding the date of your sponsorship application, if you and your co-signer are the sole owners of or partners in an uncorporated business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;c.Evidence of interest income (bank statement showing rate of interest, deposit amount and length of time deposit held), over the 12 months preceding the date of your sponsorship application, if you and your co-signer received interest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;d. Evidence of:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;investment income (e.g., dividends),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;rental income (e.g., statement of real estate rentals),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;pension income,

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;special benefits income (e.g., certificate delivered by HRDC onfirming payment of maternity, parental or sickness benefits),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;other income (give details below) received over the 12 months preceding the date of your sponsorship application, if you and your co-signer received such income.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;20.如果担保人是加拿大公民，并且居住在加拿大境外，必须提供材料，证明当你的配偶和/或子女申请永居成功后，你会和他们一起居住在加拿大；&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;21.如果随行子女是收养的子女，需要提供其身体状况声明（Medical Condition Statement）&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;申请人以及其未成年子女需要提供的文件（根据移民指南提供的列表提供文件）：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;22.身份文件；&lt;br /&gt;
23.子女信息；&lt;br /&gt;
24.旅行文件和护照；&lt;br /&gt;
25.担保人与申请人关系证明文件；&lt;br /&gt;
26.无犯罪证明原件；&lt;br /&gt;
27.体检。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;加拿大配偶和子女团聚移民 -   加拿大境外申请官方材料清单： &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cic.gc.ca/english/pdf/kits/forms/IMM5491E.pdf&#34;&gt;http://www.cic.gc.ca/english/pdf/kits/forms/IMM5491E.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;以上内容由飞出国论坛（&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com&#34;&gt;FCGvisa.com&lt;/a&gt;）独家整理完成，请尊重知识产权，转载请保留并注明出处。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>飞出国加拿大签证大全</title>
      <link>http://us.cgvisa.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://us.cgvisa.com/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;飞出国加拿大签证大全-flyabroad&#34;&gt;飞出国加拿大签证大全 - FLYabroad&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/2742/&#34;&gt;访问签证&lt;/a&gt;：&lt;a href=&#34;./2742&#34;&gt;加拿大商务访问签证-business visitor&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/2805/&#34;&gt;工作签证&lt;/a&gt;：&lt;a href=&#34;./2805&#34;&gt;加拿大工作许可综述（work permit）
&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/2557/&#34;&gt;家庭团聚移民&lt;/a&gt;：&lt;a href=&#34;./2557&#34;&gt;加拿大配偶、同居伴侣和子女团聚移民申请综述（sclpc）&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/2598/&#34;&gt;家庭团聚移民&lt;/a&gt;：&lt;a href=&#34;./2598&#34;&gt;加拿大家庭团聚移民 - 父母、祖父母团聚 pgp&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/2690/&#34;&gt;家庭团聚移民&lt;/a&gt;：&lt;a href=&#34;./2690&#34;&gt;加拿大父母和祖父母超级签证-Super Visa&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/2876/&#34;&gt;留学签证&lt;/a&gt;：&lt;a href=&#34;./2876&#34;&gt;加拿大学习许可综述 （study permit）&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/4335/&#34;&gt;魁北克签证&lt;/a&gt;：&lt;a href=&#34;./4335&#34;&gt;魁省工签(Obtaining theauthorizations to work temporarily in Québec)&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/4394/&#34;&gt;魁北克签证&lt;/a&gt;：&lt;a href=&#34;./4394&#34;&gt;魁省团聚移民 - the requirements to sponsor a close relative&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>魁省团聚移民综述 </title>
      <link>http://us.cgvisa.com/4394/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://us.cgvisa.com/4394/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;魁省家庭团聚移民:0d808498844049665100eed3aec37fb1&#34;&gt;魁省家庭团聚移民&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;担保人（飞出国）：&lt;/strong&gt;如果申请人想要担保近亲属移民魁北克，申请人必须是加拿大公民或永久居民，当前居住的魁省，年满18周岁，并且&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/prerequisites-for-sponsorship/4390/1&#34;&gt;满足一定的要求&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;被担保人&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/topic/4401/1&#34;&gt;需要满足一定的条件&lt;/a&gt;，可以是以下亲属：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;配偶、法律同居伴侣；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;受供养子女；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;父母、祖父母或外祖父母；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;18周岁以下并且未婚或者没有同居伴侣，孤儿的兄弟姐妹、侄子侄女，外省外甥女，孙子孙女，外孙子外孙女；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;打算收养的子女（国际收养）。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;担保责任和义务（飞出国）&lt;/strong&gt;：被担保人和担保人都需要&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/quebec-responsabilities-and-obligations/4400&#34;&gt;履行一定的魁省担保义务&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;担保周期：&lt;/strong&gt;根据担保类别不同，担保周期是不同的。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;担保费用 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;申请费用每年的1月份会更新。支付方式可以是：信用卡，加拿大邮政汇票，银行汇票，支票。2015年1月份发布的费用如下：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;担保一个亲属是272加币，每增加一个亲属，增加109加币。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Find out about the requirements to sponsor a close relative&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who can sponsor a close relative? Who is considered a close relative? What conditions, responsibilities and obligations are involved? What is the duration of sponsorship? What fees and timeframes are involved? To answer these questions, review all of the requirements to sponsor a close relative. Make sure that you satisfy all of these requirements before starting a sponsorship or undertaking process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sponsor (guarantor)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can sponsor a close relative if you are a Canadian citizen or permanent resident living in Québec, you are at least 18 years of age and you satisfy the prerequisites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sponsorship targets this close relative and, if applicable, accompanying family members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sponsored person (close relative)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be sponsored, your close relative must belong to the family class and satisfy specific requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can sponsor:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;your &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.immigration-quebec.gouv.qc.ca/en/immigrate-settle/sponsors-sponsored/requirements-sponsor/glossary.html&#34;&gt;spouse, common-law partner or conjugal partner &lt;/a&gt;– &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.immigration-quebec.gouv.qc.ca/en/immigrate-settle/sponsors-sponsored/requirements-sponsor/specific-requirements/index.html&#34;&gt;specific requirements&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;your&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.immigration-quebec.gouv.qc.ca/en/immigrate-settle/sponsors-sponsored/requirements-sponsor/glossary.html#enfantacharge&#34;&gt; dependent child&lt;/a&gt; – specific requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;your father, mother, grandfather or grandmother – specific requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;your orphaned brother, sister, nephew, niece, grandson or granddaughter, who is under the age of 18, and not married or in a common-law relationship – specific requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a child you plan to adopt (international adoption) – &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.immigration-quebec.gouv.qc.ca/en/immigrate-settle/sponsors-sponsored/requirements-sponsor/specific-requirements/notice-adoption.html&#34;&gt;process for adopting a child residing abroad&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities and obligations&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In undertaking the sponsorship process, both the sponsor and the sponsored person must be aware of the responsibilities and obligations they have toward each other and toward the government of Québec.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Duration of sponsorship (or undertaking)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The duration of the undertaking that you sign will vary depending on the family relationship between you (the sponsor or guarantor) and the person sponsored.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fees&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is also important that you be informed of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.immigration-quebec.gouv.qc.ca/en/immigrate-settle/sponsors-sponsored/requirements-sponsor/fees.html&#34;&gt;fees required &lt;/a&gt;to review your application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;魁省担保： &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.immigration-quebec.gouv.qc.ca/en/immigrate-settle/sponsors-sponsored/requirements-sponsor/index.html&#34;&gt;http://www.immigration-quebec.gouv.qc.ca/en/immigrate-settle/sponsors-sponsored/requirements-sponsor/index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;魁省担保要求(Prerequisites for sponsorship) - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;担保人是加拿大公民或永久居民，当前居住的魁省，年满18周岁，并且满足下列要求，可以担保其近亲属移民魁省：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;申请人必须履行了对之前被担保人的承诺。如果就业和社会团结（MESS）部发现申请人违约，那么申请人必须偿还上一个被担保人的所有社会保险和津贴，作为对其财政援助。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;除非申请人由于年龄或身体残疾导致严重伤害，长期无法工作，可以领取社会援助。否则申请人不能领取任何社会援助。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;近5年，按照法院的判决按时支付赡养费。如果没有，你必须先偿还所有欠的费用。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;没有犯罪经历，如有，需已经被释放超过5年。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;如果是担保父母、祖/外租父母，有孩子的受供养子女，或孤儿亲属，申请人必须证明有足够的财政资金，来对被担保人提供财政援助。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;不能受遣送离境令或在监狱服刑。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;不能担保未满16岁的配偶或法律同居伴侣。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;被担保人需要签署法定声明。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prerequisites for sponsorship&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must satisfy all of the following requirements, in addition to any specific requirements that apply.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must have fulfilled all previous commitments. If the Ministère de l’Emploi et de la Solidarité sociale (MESS) determines that you have defaulted, you must have repaid all of the amounts paid as financial assistance of last resort (social assistance) or special allowances to the person you sponsored.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must not receive financial assistance of last resort (social assistance) except allowances related to your age or a disability that poses obstacles to employment that are serious, permanent or of indefinite duration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Over the past five years, you must have complied with obligations arising from a judgment ordering you to pay alimony. If not, you must have repaid all outstanding amounts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must not have been convicted, in Canada or abroad, of a sexual offence, attempt or threat to commit such an offence against anyone or an offence resulting in personal injuries, or an attempt or threat to commit such an offence against a family member or relative, your spouse, common-law spouse or conjugal partner or a member of their family or relative unless you were acquitted or rehabilitated or finished serving your sentence at least five years before submitting your application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you sponsor your father, mother, grandfather, grandmother, a dependent child who has a child or a close relative who is a minor and an orphan, you must prove that you have at your disposal sufficient financial resources for the duration of the undertaking (see financial standards).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must not be subject to a removal order or detained in a penitentiary or prison.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You may not sponsor a spouse, common-law partner or conjugal partner who is under 16 years of age.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must ensure that the sponsored person, if he or she is of legal age, signs the declaration attesting that he or she fully understands the nature and scope of the undertaking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;魁省被担保亲属需满足的条件 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;除了担保人满足的基本要求外，被担保人也需要满足一定的要求：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;担保配偶：&lt;/strong&gt;配偶需年满16周岁。同时担保人对上一个配偶的担保程序已经结束。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;担保子女：&lt;/strong&gt;如果被担保的子女有孩子，需证明被担保子女财政完全依赖于担保的父母。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;担保父母、祖父母及其子女：&lt;/strong&gt;担保人需证明自己有足够的财政能力，为被担保人及其家庭成员（无论随行与否）提供财政援助。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;担保18周岁以下并且未婚或者没有同居伴侣，孤儿的兄弟姐妹、侄子侄女，外省外甥女，孙子孙女，外孙子外孙女&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;担保人必须有足够的财政能力；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;担保人还需接受当地青年中心的心理评估，以证明你有能力照顾好被担保人。评估结果转交给移民部，移民部确认你同时满足财政能力要求后，会再次转交在青年中心。评估是需要收费的。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;收养子女的要求：&lt;/strong&gt;可以参考 &lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com/t/process-for-adopting-a-child-residing-abroad/4369/1&#34;&gt;魁省国际收养流程&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the prerequisites for sponsorship, you must also take into consideration the following specific requirements pertaining to the close relative you wish to sponsor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spouse, de facto spouse or conjugal partner&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To sponsor this person, you must demonstrate that:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;your spouse, de facto spouse or conjugal partner is at least 16 years of age&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a previous undertaking to sponsor a spouse, de facto spouse or conjugal partner has come to an end.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dependent child&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the dependent child you are sponsoring has a child of his or her own, you must demonstrate your financial capacity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parents, grandparents and their dependent children&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To qualify as sponsor, you must demonstrate that:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you have the financial capacity to support the person you wish to sponsor as well as all members of that person’s family, whether or not they are accompanying the sponsored person.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brother, sister, nephew, niece, grandson, granddaughter, who is an orphan with no mother and father, under 18 years of age, and not married or a de facto spouse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To qualify as a sponsor:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you must first establish that you have the financial capacity to  support the child you wish to sponsor;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you must then undergo a psychosocial evaluation by the Centre jeunesse in your region in order to demonstrate that you are able to support and look after the child you wish to sponsor. The Ministère requests this evaluation. It then transfers it to the Centre jeunesse once it has been demonstrated that your financial capacity satisfies regulatory requirements. A fee is charged.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Child to be adopted (international adoption)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please read the information on the process for adopting a child residing abroad before beginning the process in the child’s country of origin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;魁省担保亲属需满足的条件 ： &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.immigration-quebec.gouv.qc.ca/en/immigrate-settle/sponsors-sponsored/requirements-sponsor/specific-requirements/index.html&#34;&gt;http://www.immigration-quebec.gouv.qc.ca/en/immigrate-settle/sponsors-sponsored/requirements-sponsor/specific-requirements/index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;以上内容由飞出国论坛（&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com&#34;&gt;FCGvisa.com&lt;/a&gt;）独家整理完成，请尊重知识产权，转载请保留并注明出处。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>魁省工签综述</title>
      <link>http://us.cgvisa.com/4335/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://us.cgvisa.com/4335/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;魁省工签:7408e0624a2594501d0d2a4f33558131&#34;&gt;魁省工签&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;魁省工签申请流程-飞出国:7408e0624a2594501d0d2a4f33558131&#34;&gt;魁省工签申请流程 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;根据魁省和加拿大政府之间的协议，如果申请的职业是是专业职业，并且当地劳动力无法满足雇主的需求，雇主可以使用简化的程序来处理。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;step 1. 在魁省找雇主。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;step 2. 申请人需要申请临时工作CAQ。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;申请人需要填写CAQ申请表，支付申请费191加币，并将填写完整的申请表、需要的材料，一起寄给雇主。由雇主代替申请人提交。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;备注：&lt;/strong&gt;申请费也可以由雇主支付。CAQ中填写雇主授权部分，以便雇主可以代替你提交材料。少于30天的工作不需要申请CAQ。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;step 3. 如果申请被批准，申请人需要向CIC申请工作许可。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;如果CAQ申请被拒，可以申请行政复审(request for an administrative review).在收到拒信后的90天内，将复审请求表和拒签信复印件一起寄到：
&amp;gt; Révision administrative
&amp;gt; Ministère de l&amp;rsquo;Immigration et des Communautés culturelles
&amp;gt; 285, rue Notre-Dame Ouest, 4e étage
&amp;gt; Montréal (Québec)  H2Y 1T8
&amp;gt; CANADA&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注意&lt;/strong&gt;：配偶如果打算在魁省工作、兼职学习或注册法语课程，需要获得授权。同样适用于学龄期子女。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;魁省caq-quebec-application-for-certificate-of-acceptance-caq-for-temporary-work-飞出国:7408e0624a2594501d0d2a4f33558131&#34;&gt;魁省CAQ(Quebec Application for Certificate of acceptance (CAQ) for temporary work) - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CAQ适用人群 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;外国申请人如果打算申请魁省临时技术工人或者临时低技能工人，并且持有LMIA，需要申请CAQ。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;以下情况不能申请CAQ；&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;工作种类不需要LMO即LMIA;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;从事的工作不需要工作许可；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;工作期间少于30天。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;材料邮寄给谁 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;住家护理 -第一次申请：将表格和支持文件寄到 Service
aux travailleurs temporaires, Ministère de l&amp;rsquo;Immigration et des Communautés culturelles, 285, rue Notre-Dame Ouest, 4e étage,Montréal (Québec) H2Y 1T8, Canada.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;住家护理 - 同一雇主更新申请：将表格和支持文件寄到工作所在地移民部办公室。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;住家护理 - 更换雇主（抵达后）： 将表格和支持文件寄给新的雇主。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;其他类别的技术或低技能工人：将表格和支持文件寄给新的雇主。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;随行人员 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;配偶：需持有工作或学习的授权文件。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;子女：能够参加学习，申请学习CAQ和学习许可。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;与申请工作相关的教育背景 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;提供所获得的文凭，如果无法提供，提供最后一学年的证书。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;与申请工作相关的工作经验 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;提供近5年的有偿工作经验，全职或兼职均可，包括服兵役期间和青年交换项目期间的。所提供的工作经验必须与申请职位相关。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;提供近5年内的，学徒工、培训或专业认可文凭期间的实习经验，全职或兼职，带薪或无偿的，均可。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;最新的简历。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;代理 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;不建议使用代理，如果非要使用，移民部只认可以下代理：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;members in good standing of the Barreau du Québec or the Chambre des notaires du Québec;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;persons holding a special authorization issued by the above organizations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;immigration consultants recognized by the Ministère de l’Immigration et des Communautés culturelles and registered in the Registre québécois des consultants en immigration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;其他注意事项 - 飞出国&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;所有非英文或法文的文件，都需要附上翻译件，并有认可的译员的签字。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;表格上一定要有申请人的签名，否则会被退回。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;所有递交的材料不退回。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;技术工人（Skilled worker）的定义：&lt;/strong&gt; 从事专业性、技术性或管理工作的申请人，即从事NOC 中0.A.B工作的申请人。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;低技能工人（Low-skilled worker）的定义：&lt;/strong&gt;从事半熟练或低技能工作的申请人，即从事NOC 中C.D工作的申请人。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;申请caq需要的材料清单-飞出国:7408e0624a2594501d0d2a4f33558131&#34;&gt;申请CAQ需要的材料清单 - 飞出国&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;护照首页和签名页的影印件；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;最新简历的复印件，要列出与申请职业相关的工作经验；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;和职位空缺相关的学历的影印件；&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注意：&lt;/strong&gt; CAQ填完后直接寄给雇主，需要填写Authorization given to employer 部分，以授权雇主代替你与移民部联系。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supporting documents required – Application for Certificate of acceptance for temporary work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must provide your future employer with the following supporting documents so that he or she can follow up on your application for a &lt;strong&gt;Certificate of acceptance (CAQ) for temporary work&lt;/strong&gt; from the Ministère de l&amp;rsquo;Immigration, de la Diversité et de l&amp;rsquo;Inclusion:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a photocopy of the pages of your passport that feature your name, place of birth and signature;
a copy of your latest curriculum vitæ that describes your work experience related to the job you are applying for in Québec;
a photocopy of the diplomas relevant to the job opening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Note : **You must send the Application for Certificate of acceptance (CAQ) for temporary work, duly completed and signed, &lt;strong&gt;directly to the employer&lt;/strong&gt;. Do not forget to complete the section of the Application for Certificate of acceptance (CAQ) for temporary work entitled &lt;strong&gt;Authorization given to employer&lt;/strong&gt; to authorize your employer to represent you in your process with the Ministère.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;以上内容由飞出国论坛（&lt;a href=&#34;http://bbs.fcgvisa.com&#34;&gt;FCGvisa.com&lt;/a&gt;）独家整理完成，请尊重知识产权，转载请保留并注明出处。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>